<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vandana Verma</title>
    <link>https://infosecvandana.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vandana Verma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Vandana Verma</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://infosecvandana.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 19 - OWASP Application Security Verification standard (ASVS)</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight19/</guid>
      <description>OWASP Spotlight - Project 19 - OWASP Application Security Verification standard (ASVS)
About the Project:-
The OWASP Application Security Verification Standard (ASVS) Project provides a basis for testing web application technical security controls and also provides developers with a list of requirements for secure development.
The primary aim of the OWASP Application Security Verification Standard (ASVS) Project is to normalize the range in the coverage and level of rigor available in the market when it comes to performing Web application security verification using a commercially-workable open standard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 12 - Pawan Desai</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/pawandesai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/pawandesai/</guid>
      <description>Pawan Desai
https://www.linkedin.com/in/pawan-desai-5455562/
https://twitter.com/pawandesai
Bio:-
Co-founder &amp;amp; CEO - MitKat Advisory Services, Cyber Security, IVLP fellow, Submariner, Advisor AllMiles, Visiting faculty at NMIMS MitKat Risk Intelligence and Monitoring Engine, Certified Corporate Director
Learning for Mentees:
  Do what you love
  Mediocrity will kill the culture, Don&amp;rsquo;t accept Mediocrity, Work with people who want to work for a cause
  Your work doesn&amp;rsquo;t define you. To be known for is who and what you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2 - Lakshmi Hanspal</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/ciso/lakshmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/ciso/lakshmi/</guid>
      <description>Lakshmi Hanspal
https://www.linkedin.com/in/lakshmi-hanspal/
Bio:-
Lakshmi Hanspal is the Global Chief Security Officer of Box, leading the Trust Office for Box across multiple security and privacy domains including Corporate, Physical, Cyber, Customer, Product, Platform, Risk &amp;amp; Assurance, Compliance and Data Protection. Lakshmi is a persuasive and recognized executive leader who provides overall transformational leadership for security strategies, with emphasis on cloud security, risk and privacy management. She has strong ability to engage with customers and senior level executives across the organization and influence buy in and consensus on key initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 11 - Aseem Jakhar</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/aseem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/aseem/</guid>
      <description>Aseem Jakhar
https://www.linkedin.com/in/aseemjakhar/
https://twitter.com/aseemjakhar
Bio:-
Entrepreneur | IoT security | Co-Founder - Payatu, hardwear.io, nullcon.net, null.co.in | Author - EXPLIoT framework
Learning for Mentees:
Try, Fail, Try Again - You will win</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1 - Sarb Sembhi</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/ciso/sarb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/ciso/sarb/</guid>
      <description>Sarb Sembhi
https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarbsembhi/
Bio:-
Sarb is a CTO &amp;amp; CISO speaking, writing and contributing to many events and publications. He is the Founder of the Security2Live Initiative (which raises Digital Safety Skills). He Mentors Cyber Security Start-ups (and help with getting them into the market) and other start-ups as the Cyber Security advisor, and am a Board Advisor to several companies. In 2020, he was honoured to be shortlisted 5 in the IFSecGlobal 2020 20 Most Influential People in Security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 10 - Shubham Mittal </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shubham/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shubham/</guid>
      <description>Shubham Mittal
https://www.linkedin.com/in/upgoingstar/ https://twitter.com/upgoingstar
Bio:-
Co-Founder at RedHunt Labs | BlackHat Asia Review Board Member
Learning for Mentees:-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 9 - Aaron Rinehart</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/aaronrinehart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/aaronrinehart/</guid>
      <description>Aaron Rinehart
https://twitter.com/aaronrinehart
https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaronsrinehart/
Bio:-
Aaron has been expanding the possibilities of Chaos Engineering in its application to other safety- critical portions of the IT domain notably cybersecurity. He began pioneering the application of Security in Chaos Engineering during his tenure as the Chief Security Architect at the largest private healthcare company in the world, UnitedHealth Group (UHG). While at UHG Aaron released ChaoSlingr, one of the first open source software releases focused on using Chaos Engineering in cybersecurity to build more resilient systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 18 - OWASP DSOMM</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight18/</guid>
      <description>OWASP Spotlight - Project 18 - OWASP DSOMM
About the Project:-
The DevSecOps Maturity Model, shows security measures which are applied when using DevOps strategies and how these can be prioritized. With the help of DevOps strategies security can also be enhanced. For example, each component such as application libraries and operating system libraries in docker images can be tested for known vulnerabilities. Attackers are intelligent and creative, equipped with new technologies and purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 7 - Dhillon Kannabhiran</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/dhillon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/dhillon/</guid>
      <description>Dhillon Kannabhiran
https://www.linkedin.com/in/l33tdawg/
Bio:-
Dhillon Andrew Kannabhiran (@l33tdawg on Twitter) is the Founder and Chief Executive Officer of Hack in The Box (http://www.hitb.org), organiser of the HITBSecConf series of network security conferences which has been held annually for over a decade in various countries including Malaysia, The Netherlands and the UAE.
Prior to quitting his day job to lead the HITB team on crazy adventures around the world, Dhillon started off at the height of the dotcom craze as a technology journalist with PC World, ZDnet, MIS Asia and CNet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 8 - Amar Singh</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/amarsingh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/amarsingh/</guid>
      <description>Amar Singh
https://www.linkedin.com/in/chiefinfosec/
Bio:-
Amar Singh is a CEO, CISO, Cyber Crisis &amp;amp; Incident Response Practitioner, Speaker &amp;amp; Co-Founder Cyber Management Alliance.
Amar is an industry acknowledged expert and public speaker and is regularly invited to speak and share his insights by some of the largest and most respected organisations in the world including The BBC, The Economist’s Intelligence Unit, The Financial Times, SC Magazine, InfoSec Magazine, Computer Weekly, The Register and the Al-Jazeera English Channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 17 - Education and Training Committee</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight17/</guid>
      <description>OWASP Spotlight - Project 17 - Education and Training Committee
About the Committee
To provide a support mechanism for OWASP education activities to foster collaborations and supporting relationships with the Application Security, Developer and Training communities both academic and industry based.
Helps to advise the Foundation &amp;amp; Board of an educational strategy for OWASP. We should be leading the world in the sector.
About Education and Training Committee Information
Email: education-and-training-committee@owasp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AISA Webinar: Shifting left in application security </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/aisa2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/aisa2021/</guid>
      <description>It was a pleasure to be part of the ONLINE PANEL: &amp;lsquo;Shifting Left in Application Security&amp;rsquo; at Australian Information Security Association (AISA) this morning with the wonderful co- panelists
◼ Teuta H Hyseni
◼ Nancy Gariché
◼ Vandana Verma Sehgal (myself)
Incredible discussion around DevSecOps-oriented application security programme, cloud-first strategy, Zero Trust and DevSecOps for legacy applications.
Date: Wednesday 19 May 2021
Time Zones:
11:30am - 12:30pm AEST (Brisbane, Canberra, Melbourne, Sydney &amp;amp; Hobart) 11:00am - 12:00pm ACST (Adelaide) 9:30am - 10:30am AWST (Perth)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSA Conference 2021</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/rsa2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/rsa2021/</guid>
      <description>My First RSA Conference this year and I got the opportunity to be part of the conf in many ways. Lot of learning, takeaways, meeting virtually with amazing people.
 ITSPmagazine Podcast Interview at Media section with the very amazing Keren Elazari   Lightening talk for WeAreHackerz at RSA on “Careers in #AppSec: Lead with Grit”  BIRDS OF A FEATHER at Career Path (Technical Track) - Incredible discussion around Open source Software Security in the enterprise environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consumer identities in Modern Digital World (CIAM)</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/ciam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/ciam/</guid>
      <description>Digitization is the way to go However, while the consumers are increasing, we still follow the primitive approach and have always been taking too much information from the users like Email Address, Username, Address, Password and much more during the first interaction itself.
At the same time, security is becoming equally big concern for the organizations and users. Usability is severely impacted with applying the highest level of security on every user interaction which results in a poor user experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6 - Keenan Skelly</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/keenan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/keenan/</guid>
      <description>Keenan Skelly
https://www.linkedin.com/in/keenan-skelly/
Bio:-
• Co-Founder &amp;amp; CEO - shyftED, Inc.
• President and CEO - Spark Security Solutions, Inc
• Strategic Advisor to CEO - Circadence Corp.
• Director, Board of Directors – Night Lion Security
• Advisor, Women in Cybersecurity Advisory Council – SC Media
• Games Master - Women’s Society of Cyberjutsu
Ms. Skelly has twenty years’ experience in providing security and management solutions across a wide array of platforms to include personnel, physical, and cyber security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 5 - Mari Galloway</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/mari/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/mari/</guid>
      <description>Mari Galloway
https://www.linkedin.com/in/themarigalloway/
https://twitter.com/marigalloway
Bio:-
Mari is the CEO and a founding board member for the Women&amp;rsquo;s Society of Cyberjutsu (WSC), one of the fastest growing 501c3 non-profit cybersecurity communities dedicated to bringing more women and girls to cyber. WSC provides its members with the resources and support required to enter and advance as a cybersecurity professional. Mari began her cyber career with Accenture where she excelled as a Network Engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 4 - Takaharu Ogasa</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/takaharu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/takaharu/</guid>
      <description>Takaharu Ogasa https://twitter.com/TakaharuOgasa https://www.linkedin.com/in/takaharu-ogasa-a245b7b5/
Bio: Takaharu is the Founder of Security Initiative, a start-up and a Cyber Security consultancy. He is also the chapter leader for OWASP Sandai Chapter.
Learning for the Mentees:-
Link to the Previous Episodes: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R75Oye_LIaI&amp;amp;list=PLUKo5k_oSrfMzA0_VbOJjKh1AViSYcNrr</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 16 - Cornucopia</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight16/</guid>
      <description>OWASP Spotlight - Project 16 - Cornucopia
About the Project:- OWASP Foundation Cornucopia is a mechanism in the form of a card game to assist software development teams identify security requirements in Agile, conventional and formal development processes. It is language, platform and technology agnostic. The idea behind Cornucopia is to help development teams, especially those using Agile methodologies, to identify application security requirements and develop security-based user stories.
Getting Involved Involvement in the development is actively encouraged!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3 - Bryson Bort</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/bryson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/bryson/</guid>
      <description>Bio:
Bryson is the Founder of SCYTHE, a start-up building a next generation attack emulation platform, and GRIMM, a cybersecurity consultancy, and Co-Founder of the ICS Village, a non-profit advancing awareness of industrial control system security. He is a Senior Fellow for Cybersecurity and National Security at R Street and the National Security Institute and an Advisor to the Army Cyber Institute. As a U.S. Army Officer, he served as a Battle Captain and Brigade Engineering Officer in support of Operation Iraqi Freedom before leaving the Army as a Captain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 15 - Dependency Track</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight15/</guid>
      <description>About the Project:- Dependency-Track is an intelligent Component Analysis platform that allows organizations to identify and reduce risk in the software supply chain. Dependency-Track takes a unique and highly beneficial approach by leveraging the capabilities of Software Bill of Materials (SBOM). This approach provides capabilities that traditional Software Composition Analysis (SCA) solutions cannot achieve.
Some of the ways you can help are as follows:
 Try it out Have your development team try it out Submit feedback via Github issues Submit pull requests  References:-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vice-Chairperson - OWASP Global Board of Directors</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/advisoryboard/owasp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/advisoryboard/owasp/</guid>
      <description>Reference link:
https://owasp.org/corporate/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Asia Review Board</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/advisoryboard/blackhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/advisoryboard/blackhat/</guid>
      <description>Reference link:
https://www.blackhat.com/asia-21/review-board.html#Vandana-Verma</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2 - Shira Shamban</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shira/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shira/</guid>
      <description>Shira Shamban
https://twitter.com/ShambanIT​
Bio:
Shira Shamban is a security researcher and technical expert with a focus on cloud security. Currently, she is the co-founder and CEO of Solvo. Shira started her professional career in #cybersecurity​ as a military officer in the elite intelligence unit 8200 of the Israel Defense Force. During her 13-year service in the unit, Shira acquired hands-on experience in cybersecurity and intelligence operations while earning an engineering degree from Tel-Aviv University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 14 - Secure Coding Dojo</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight14/</guid>
      <description>About the Project:- The Secure Coding Dojo is a training platform which can be customized to integrate with custom vulnerable websites and other CTF challenges.
Getting Involved Involvement in the development and promotion of Secure Coding Dojo is actively encouraged! You do not have to be a security expert or a programmer to contribute. Some of the ways you can help are as follows:
 Try it out Have your development team try it out Submit feedback via Github issues Submit pull requests  References:- OWASP Secure Coding Dojo Main Project Page: https://owasp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1 - Shivangi Nadkarni</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shivangi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shivangi/</guid>
      <description>Shivani Nadkarni (Co-founder &amp;amp; CEO - Arrka)
https://twitter.com/shivanginadkarn​
Bio: Shivangi has over 24 years of experience in the domains of Information Security &amp;amp; Risk Management, E-Commerce &amp;amp; Networking across multiple geographies. She has earlier worked with organizations like Wipro &amp;amp; Sify handling a variety of roles and heading different Lines of Business. She was instrumental in setting up the first licensed Certifying Authority in India – in association with VeriSign. She has authored the Privacy Book of Knowledge (PBoK) for DSCI for their DCPP certification program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 13 - Mobile Security Testing Guide</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight13/</guid>
      <description>About the Project:-
The MSTG is a comprehensive manual for mobile app security testing and reverse engineering for iOS and Android mobile security testers with the following content: *Mobile platform internals
*Security testing in the mobile app development lifecycle *Basic static and dynamic security testing *Mobile app #reverseengineering​ and tampering #Assessing​ software protections
Detailed test cases that map to the requirements in the MASVS.
References:-
OWASP Mobile Security Testing Guide Main Project Page: https://owasp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7th Annual DynamicCISO Excellence Award Resilient CISO</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/ciso/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/ciso/</guid>
      <description>The goal was to choose a set of CISOs and InfoSec leaders who have demonstrated an extraordinary leadership and resilience during the challenging times
Reference
www.cisosummit.co.in</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CQ 100: Meet The Dynamic Women Changing The Face Of Indian Cyberspace</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/top100indian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/top100indian/</guid>
      <description>SC Media, Women in IT Security Advocates Award
Reference
https://www.the420.in/meet-the-dynamic-women-changing-the-face-of-indian-cyberspace/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote speaker for Cyber Security Warriors Club Opening</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/vitbhopal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/vitbhopal/</guid>
      <description>Colleges are doing exceptional work towards bringing cyber security closer to the students. Once such incident, I witnessed over the weekend, where I was invited to VIT Bhopal University as a Chief Guest and #keynote speaker at the launch of the VIT Bhopal Cyber Warriors Club where I shared my views around Careers in Cyber Security and what students can do make the future shine for our country.
It such a heartwarming experience to see the College Management going extra mile for the students to motivate the students to innovate in different faces of cyber security from creating CTF&amp;rsquo;s hardware, software to creating something totally incredible with #AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote: Careers in AppSec: Lead with Grit</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/careerinappsec_mit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/careerinappsec_mit/</guid>
      <description>Closing the Skill Gap With More Women in Cybersecurity
To gain an insight into the lack of women representation, CISO MAG gauged a few women security influencers to understand the cause of this alarming trend. This article is part of a series of interviews from women cybersecurity experts who shed light representation of women in cybersecurity.
Reference https://cisomag.eccouncil.org/closing-the-skill-gap-with-more-women-in-cybersecurity/3/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with CISO MAG</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/cisomag_2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/cisomag_2021/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating Women in Cyber Security
To gain an insight into the lack of women representation, CISO MAG gauged a few women security influencers to understand the cause of this alarming trend. This article is part of a series of interviews from women cybersecurity experts who shed light representation of women in cybersecurity.
Reference https://cisomag.eccouncil.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/CISO-MAG_Mar_2021_Preview.pdf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrate ‘You’ - Be relentless, fearless, voice out!</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/relentlessyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/relentlessyou/</guid>
      <description>Let’s start with a beautiful quote by Ruth Bader Ginsburg -“Women will have achieved true equality when men share with them the responsibility of bringing up the next generation”. 2020 has taught that a family can have 2 heroes in the same home and share responsibilities while meting differences. Supporting and uplifting each other, leads to co-growth which can be a strong influence personally and the backbone for a positive career path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 12 - Zed Attack Proxy (ZAP)</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight12/</guid>
      <description>About the Project:- The OWASP Zed Attack Proxy (ZAP) is one of the world’s most popular free security tools and is actively maintained by a dedicated international team of volunteers. It can help you automatically find security vulnerabilities in your web applications while you are developing and testing your applications. It&amp;rsquo;s also a great tool for experienced pen-testers to use for manual security testing.
References:- OWASP Zed Attack Proxy (ZAP) - https://owasp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grace Hopper Celebration 2021 - India</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/ghci2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/ghci2021/</guid>
      <description>Fri Feb 26, 11:00 AM - 11:45 AM GMT +5.5 (45 Min)
[Track : Security &amp;amp; Privacy]
Title : Redefining Trust in Security
If you ask a security expert on “how to protect their network” they would mostly say “firewalls&#39;&#39;. It may not be enough for today’s environment. The landscape has significantly changed due to the perimeters having disappeared; people can login remotely, cloud has stepped in; everyone is a tenant on a shared server, digital transformation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote: Digital Week: Effective AppSec Program w/ Open Source (OWASP) Projects</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/digitalweek/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/digitalweek/</guid>
      <description>Joined Digital Week: Southeast Asia as a #keynotespeaker
Four-day virtual conference from 23-26 February is a chance for all of us in the Cloud, Datacenter, and Cybersecurity industries to discuss innovations and developments across the ASEAN region.
Checkout the conversation: https://bit.ly/2N4V1jV</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridge the gap between AI/ML and Cyber Security</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/sabudh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/sabudh/</guid>
      <description>Student Session: Bridge the gap between AI/ML and Cyber Security
Session on Embedding AI/ML with Cyber Security with Sabudh Foundation for BML Munjal University (BMU), Haryana
Vandana speaks on 20th February at 11a.m. on &amp;ldquo;Embedding AI/ML with Cyber Security&amp;rdquo;. To attend, register at:
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Testing Workshop 2021 for CSQA</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/securitytestingqa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/securitytestingqa/</guid>
      <description>About the Workshop
Showcasing Security Testing essentials, OWASP Project, different tools and approaches for Security Testing.
Attendees will learn:
 What is Application security Testing and its importance OWASP Security Testing Projects, tools and approaches How to start with Security Testing  Reference Link: https://www.townscript.com/e/csqa-security-test-workshop
Video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Borders Advisory Board Member - SiberX</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/advisoryboard/siberx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/advisoryboard/siberx/</guid>
      <description>Reference link:
https://www.siberx.org/event/women-in-cybersecurity-beyond-borders/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EC-Council Advisory Board for CND</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/advisoryboard/eccouncil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/advisoryboard/eccouncil/</guid>
      <description>Reference link:
https://www.eccouncil.org/cnd-advisory-board/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Roundtable hosted by the ISRM Women in Security Sisterhood group.</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/isrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/isrm/</guid>
      <description>Global Roundtable hosted by the ISRM Women in Security Sisterhood group.
The subject of Women in Technology is one that is at the forefront of multiple vectors, including diversity, equality, and need to encourage girls to take up STEM subjects.
One way to encourage that is to give examples of inspirational women who have achieved incredible things in their own fields.
Moderator - Danyetta Fleming Magana
Panelists
Dr. Amelia Estwick, Director, National Cybersecurity Institute, spent over 20 years in the INFOSEC/cybersecurity field with the Department of Defense /National Security Agency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 LENS INTO CYBERSECURITY TRENDS</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/2021lens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/2021lens/</guid>
      <description>2020 was a year like never before. We all witnessed the twists and turns in our lives. It did have a torrential impact on the cyber security ecosystem too. Although everyone quickly adapted to the new world and embraced the use of technology to work from home, but deep down it meant there was a whole new attack to be guarded against- inadequate preparedness. This led to the paradigm shift from the highly forecasted AI and ML taking precedence whereas it was cloud migration or computing taking the top priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Session: Social Media safety</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/ignite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/ignite/</guid>
      <description>This International Day of Women and Girls in Science. I got an opportunity to train over 200 college girls around Social Media safety along with the IGNITE Worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panel on Application Security Testing</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/techjs_summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/techjs_summit/</guid>
      <description>Panel discussion - Application Security Testing
Schedule: Jan 28, 19:30-20:10 CET
Invited panelists:
  Scott Gerlach (CSO &amp;amp; Co-Founder @ StackHawk)
  Sam Stepanyan (OWASP London Chapter Leader &amp;amp; Independent Application Security Consultant)
  Liran Tal (Developer Advocate @ Snyk &amp;amp; Node.js Foundation Security Working Group)
  Bar Hofesh (Co-Founder, CTO &amp;amp; Security Researcher @ NeuraLegion)
  Moderator:
Vandana Verma Sehgal
  The focus of the panel discussion we planned to have but are open to discuss your ideas as well (if you join us):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INSPIRE 20 Leadership Podcast</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/techbeacon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/techbeacon/</guid>
      <description>INSPIRE 20 Podcast: Vandana Verma Sehgal, Infosec Girls
Reference
https://techbeacon.com/enterprise-it/inspire-20-podcast-vandana-verma-sehgal-infosec-girls?utm_source=richisoc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspire 20 - Vandana Verma</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/podcasts/inspire20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/podcasts/inspire20/</guid>
      <description>In the podcast, Verma explains why mentorship is so critical in addressing gender imbalance in the tech industry, and what it means to &amp;ldquo;uplift others,&amp;rdquo; help them conquer their fears, and guide them in the right direction.
EP15: Vandana Verma Sehgal, Board of Directors at OWASP &amp;amp; President InfosecGirls by INSPIRE 20 is licensed under a Creative Commons License.
https://soundcloud.com/user-699370465/inspire-20-vandana-verma-infosec-girls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discussion on Cyberthreats and Darkweb scare</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/iitk_alumani/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/iitk_alumani/</guid>
      <description>Alumni Association of IIT Kanpur Delhi Chapter cordially invites you all to benefit from the Webinar on Cyberthreats and Darkweb scare while working from home on Saturday 16th Jan 2021 from 5.30 PM to 6.30 PM.
Moderated By
  Mr. Sameer Nigam ( CEO Stratbeans/ IIT Kanpur 96 /IIM A 06)
  Ms Sneha Rahar ( Manager, American Express/ IIT Kanpur 2016)
  Panelists:
  Prof Sandeep Shukla IIT Kanpur</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Session: Cyber Ethics and Privacy</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/dpsbangalore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/dpsbangalore/</guid>
      <description>I got an opportunity to speak to DPS Bangalore East students on #cyberethics #privacy and #hackingstrategies as part of 1M1B (1 Million for 1 Billion) initiative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Security 2021 Prediction</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/csw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/csw/</guid>
      <description>Reference
https://cybersecurityworks.com/cyber-security-predictions-2021/vandana-verma.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 11 - Nettacker</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight11/</guid>
      <description>This project is an automated penetration testing tool, but it can be used for all sorts of interesting things because it is modular and basically it&amp;rsquo;s written in Python, and it allows you to do three different things. So it allows us to Perform scans Of the network. Originally it was created as an IoT scanner to scan IoT devices. So you can scan the network, it can discover your service your hosts, it can scan for open ports and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t really quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Society for Data Science: Spice of Data Analytics in Cyber Security</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/icdmai2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/icdmai2021/</guid>
      <description>The Society for Data Science team is back with an exciting set of Workshops and Tutorials as a part of ICDMAI 2021 to happen on 15th January 2021.
Join the Workshops on Spice of Data Analytics in Cyber Security by Vandana Verma Sehgal on 15th January 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 10 - Top10</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight10/</guid>
      <description>The OWASP Top 10 is a standard awareness document for developers and web application security. It represents a broad consensus about the most critical security risks to web applications.
Globally recognized by developers as the first step towards more secure coding. Companies should adopt this document and start the process of ensuring that their web applications minimize these risks. Using the OWASP Top 10 is perhaps the most effective first step towards changing the software development culture within your organization into one that produces more secure code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec Influencer of 2020 Award</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/appsecinfluencer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/appsecinfluencer/</guid>
      <description>Reference - WhiteSource https://twitter.com/WhiteSourceSoft/status/1345009431252242432?s=20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building an AppSec Program with Open Source</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/owaspny/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/owaspny/</guid>
      <description>Building an AppSec Program with Open Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 9 - Software Assurance Maturity Model (SAMM)</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight9/</guid>
      <description>About the Project:- The Software Assurance Maturity Model (SAMM) is an open framework to help organizations formulate and implement a strategy for software security that is tailored to the specific risks facing the organization. SAMM helps you:
 Evaluate an organization’s existing software security practices Build a balanced software security assurance program in well-defined iterations Demonstrate concrete improvements to a security assurance program Define and measure security-related activities throughout an organization  References:-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 8 - Proactive Controls</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight8/</guid>
      <description>About the Project:-
The OWASP Top Ten Proactive Controls describes the most important control and control categories that every architect and developer should absolutely, 100% include in every project.
OWASP Proactive Controls - https://owasp.org/www-project-proactive-controls/
Contributing to Proactive Controls - https://github.com/OWASP/www-project-proactive-controls/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Owasp can help Security Teams - Guides and Testing Tools</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/owasptestingtools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/owasptestingtools/</guid>
      <description>How Owasp can help Security Teams - Guides and Testing Tools - 8th December 2020
By Dinis Cruz, Sam Stepanyan, Grant Ongers and Vandana Verma
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 7 -  Security Knowledge Framework </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight7/</guid>
      <description>Hi Everyone.
We are back again with another spotlight series project and today we have OWASP Security Knowledge Framework (SKF) with us. I feel that this is one project, which is so much relevant and this is required in any organization for training the developers, security researchers, for getting the requirements and whatnot.
The security framework wants to help developers &amp;amp; empower them, to be able to give them the right awareness and knowledge to build secure applications by design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote: DevSecOps Days London</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/devopsdays_london/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/devopsdays_london/</guid>
      <description>Title: Running a devsecops pipeline with open source projects
Reference:- https://www.devsecopsdays.com/2020-devsecops-days-london</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadening the diversity aperture</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/scmagazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/scmagazine/</guid>
      <description>Reference:-
scmagazine.com/women-in-it-security/women-advocates/vandana-verma-broadening-the-diversity-aperture/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Featured in TimesofIndia</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/timesofindia_techies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/timesofindia_techies/</guid>
      <description>Times webinar on cybersecurity and women hackers
Reference</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 6 -  PyTM </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight6/</guid>
      <description>We are back again with another oversaw spotlight series project, and this time we have a very interesting project, which is around Threat Modeling.
Fixing the bugs later in the stage can cost huge money. Now, when we all started talking about DevOps or DevSecOps, So it&amp;rsquo;s imperative that we bring in the Threat Model in #cloud, which is automated which have which have less of work for us, especially for testers for developers for anyone, Who is a part of the application development lifecycle and even for architects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Crime against Women: Precautions and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/mizoramuni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/mizoramuni/</guid>
      <description>I had the pleasure to speak at one of the National webinar organised by Mizoram University on “Cyber Crime against Women: Precautions and Strategies” with the esteemed speaker.
YouTube Link - https://lnkd.in/gP56TCB
Huge shoutout to Department of Management, Mizoram University under the support of National Commission for Women (NCW), New Delhi
#cybersecurity #datasecurity National Commission for Women #ncw</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Factor Security Interview with Vandana Verma</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/humanfactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/humanfactor/</guid>
      <description>In this interview Jenny talks to the multi award winning women&amp;rsquo;s advocate and member of OWASP global board of directors, Vandana Verma. They discuss her career in cyber, her promotion of women through groups like InfosecGirls, and how the pandemic has impacted cybersecurity in India and beyond. Thank you for an amazing interview, Vandana.
Reference</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps for RazorPay</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/razorpay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/razorpay/</guid>
      <description>Webinar: Cybersecurity Trends &amp;amp; Women in Ethical Hacking | #TimesTechiesWebinars
In this week&amp;rsquo;s edition of #TimesTechiesWebinars, watch India&amp;rsquo;s leading women ethical hackers speak about the current trends in cybersecurity and the plethora of options and guidance for women seeking a career in ethical hacking.
The session features:
Vandana Verma, Security Solutions Architect - IBM ISL
Amrin Maria Khan Adawadkar, Security - Identity and Access Management at IBM India
Ashwini Varadkar, Sr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Times Techies Webinars</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/timestechies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/timestechies/</guid>
      <description>Webinar: Cybersecurity Trends &amp;amp; Women in Ethical Hacking | #TimesTechiesWebinars
In this week&amp;rsquo;s edition of #TimesTechiesWebinars, watch India&amp;rsquo;s leading women ethical hackers speak about the current trends in cybersecurity and the plethora of options and guidance for women seeking a career in ethical hacking.
The session features:
Vandana Verma, Security Solutions Architect - IBM ISL
Amrin Maria Khan Adawadkar, Security - Identity and Access Management at IBM India
Ashwini Varadkar, Sr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 5 -  SecurityRAT</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight5/</guid>
      <description>Gathering the requirements and tracking them is always a challenge in the application development. The biggest concern area is if the security requirement changes then to track them.
The next project as part of OWASP Spotlight series helps in gathering the requirements and cherry on top of cake in automating them. SecurityRAT simplifies the security requirement management during development using automation approaches.
About the Project:-
OWASP SecurityRAT - https://owasp.org/www-project-securityrat/
Official Website CRS - https://securityrat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 4 - Cheat Sheet Series</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight4/</guid>
      <description>About the Project:-
The OWASP Cheat Sheet Series was created to provide a set of simple good practice guides for application developers and defenders to follow. Rather than focused on detailed best practices that are impractical for many developers and applications, they are intended to provide good practices that the majority of developers will actually be able to implement.
References:-
OWASP Cheat Sheet Series - https://owasp.org/www-project-cheat-sheets/
More Details - https://cheatsheetseries.owasp.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 3 - Core Rule Set (CRS)</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight3/</guid>
      <description>About the Project:- The OWASP ModSecurity Core Rule Set (CRS) is a set of generic attack detection rules for use with ModSecurity or compatible web application firewalls. The CRS aims to protect web applications from a wide range of attacks, including the OWASP Top Ten, with a minimum of false alerts. The CRS provides protection against many common attack categories, including SQL Injection, Cross Site Scripting, Local File Inclusion, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiring Leaders at IBM India</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/ibm/</guid>
      <description>Inspiring Leaders at IBM India Interview
&amp;ldquo;It is my second stint with IBM, and I would call it fate, as I was not looking for a change and suddenly got a call from IBM for a profile which I felt, was relevant for me. I gave the interview and once again became an IBMer in 2017. IBM has given me a playground to experiment with the technology, and being with India Software labs makes me enjoy the technology even more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epic Women in Cyber — Vandana Verma</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/epicwoman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/epicwoman/</guid>
      <description>https://medium.com/epic-women-in-cyber/epic-women-in-cyber-vandana-verma-173c0775c3fe</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SC Media - Women in IT Security - Advocates Award - 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/scmedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/scmedia/</guid>
      <description>SC Media, Women in IT Security Advocates Award
![SC media](/images/SC media.png)
Reference
https://www.scmagazine.com/women-in-it-security/women-advocates/vandana-verma-broadening-the-diversity-aperture/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROOTCON: Zero Trust in the era of cloud</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/rootcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/rootcon/</guid>
      <description>Title : Applying OWASP Web Security Testing Guide by Vandana Verma - 12 Jun
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Security: Past, Present, and Future</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/cybersentinelupes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/cybersentinelupes/</guid>
      <description>“Cybersecurity is much more than an IT topic.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 2 - Dependency Check</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight2/</guid>
      <description>OWASP has so many amazing and great projects which can help organisations, developers, security testers and many more groups. However, working with OWASP projects very closely in the past few years, I have realised people do not know about a lot of projects or even have no clue if they exist.
So, here I am writing the part series on OWASP Projects with a video describing about the project. This is the second blog as part of the OWASP Spotlight Series talking about OWASP Dependency Check.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global AppSec 2020 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/globalappsecsf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/globalappsecsf/</guid>
      <description>About the Training
This Training is intended for students/professionals interested in making a career in the Information Security domain. This training involves real world scenarios that every Security Professional must be well versed with. It involves decompiling, real-time analyzing and testing of the applications from security standpoint.
Reference https://events.bizzabo.com/OWASPGlobalAppSec/agenda/session/325430</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integration Reciepe : IBM IGI with IBM Security Verify </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/recipe_igiverify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/recipe_igiverify/</guid>
      <description>Recently I have been experimenting with various IBM product integrations and I posted a reciepe in IBM Community portal for integration of IBM IGI with IBM Security Verify.
This recipe talks about the ideal set of steps that someone has to take to connect the two applications.
Here is a direct link to the article.
Recipe for IBM Security Verify Governance (IGI) and IBM Security Verify for Workforce IAM Integration</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Spotlight - Project 1 - Web Security Testing Guide</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight1/</guid>
      <description>OWASP has so many amazing and great projects which can help organisations, developers, security testers and many more groups. However, working with OWASP projects very closely in the past few years, I have realised people do not know about a lot of projects or even have no clue if they exist.
So, here I am writing the part series on OWASP Projects with a video describing about the project. This is the first blog as part of the OWASP Project Series talking about OWASP Web Security Testing Guide (OWSTG).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Asia 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/blackhatasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/blackhatasia/</guid>
      <description>Reference Link: Black Hat Asia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Cybersecurity Magazine</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/cybersecuritymagazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 18:23:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/cybersecuritymagazine/</guid>
      <description>Interview with Cybersecurity Magazine
Reference https://cybersecurity-magazine.com/interview-with-vandana-verma-from-infosec-girls/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IAM in eCommerce - Deal or No Deal</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/iam_commercebytes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/iam_commercebytes/</guid>
      <description>Users always wants to make sure they have everything is working, they are able to use the website and at the same time their identities are secure. There is a huge shift in the traditional Identity and access management and now with the time, we have to modernize the Identities. We are talking about consumer IAM as well.
I had the opportunity to speak at #commercebytes platform with the e-commerce owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact of COVID-19 on Cloud Adoption &amp; Security</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/csasummit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/csasummit/</guid>
      <description>Impact of COVID-19 on Cloud Adoption &amp;amp; Security at CSA India Annual Summit
The onset of the pandemic has thrown normalcy out of gear. There is talk of a “new normal”, which continues to be defined and remains as broad as ever. The synapse between the COVID-19 pandemic and cloud security imperatives can be addressed with a call to action that the new cyber &amp;amp; cloud security strategy on the anvil can address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STEM FOR GIRLS </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/stemforgirls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/stemforgirls/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winner - Cyber Security Woman of the Year Award 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/cybersecawards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/cybersecawards/</guid>
      <description>Reference
https://cybersecurityawards.com/2020-winners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSA UK: Cloud Security and Identity and Access management</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/csauk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/csauk/</guid>
      <description>Moderator -
Panelists</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Empowering tips on Online Safety for Working Women</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/emergingtipsforwomen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/emergingtipsforwomen/</guid>
      <description>Moderator - Dr. Chandra Vadhana R, Founder &amp;amp; Director Prayaana Labs
Panelists
  Sanjay Kumar IPS, DIG Range Trivandrum
  Vandana Verma, OWASP Global Board of Directors
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judge and Jury for Top 20 Indian Women Influencers in Security 2020 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/judgejury/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/judgejury/</guid>
      <description>Dr Kiran Bedi was in her element as the Chief Guest
The jury comprised of
• Mr Rajan Luthra, Chairman’s Office – Head-Special Projects, Reliance Industries Ltd.
• Dr. Shailja Vaidya Gupta, Senior Adviser – Office of the Principal Scientific Adviser to Government of India
• Ms Bonnie Butlin, Co-founder &amp;amp; Executive Director, Security Partners Forum
• Ms Aman Singh, Publisher SECURITY TODAY &amp;amp; SECURITY UPDATE
• Ms Vandana Verma, President, Infosec Girls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Cybersecurity Strategy - Indo-Pacific Series - Episode 2</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/malaysian_panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/malaysian_panel/</guid>
      <description>Indo-Pacific Series - reviewing the Australian Cyber Security Strategy and making Women in Security announcements
Moderator - Chris Cubbage
Panelists
  Ron Gauci GAICD
  Sean Duca
  Ian Yip,
  Dr Carrine Teoh Chooi Shi
  Vandana Verma and
  Raman Sopory
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running an AppSec Program with Open Source (OWASP) Projects</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/runningappsecprogram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/runningappsecprogram/</guid>
      <description>We are all heading towards modernisation of applications. However, we still see the vulnerabilities like SQL Injection, Sensitive data exposure, and security misconfiguration etc. When the loopholes in applications (such as legacy, desktop, web, mobile, micro services) are exploited, it can give malicious actors access to the organisation&amp;rsquo;s data.
This is a fact that Breaches will happen and security flaws will exist, however what we can do is minimise the chances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be an InfoSec Speaker - Vandana Verma</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/podcasts/howtobeinfosecspeaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/podcasts/howtobeinfosecspeaker/</guid>
      <description>There are still lots of misconceptions and myths about Cloud Security. In this episode , Vandana Verma Global Board of Directors at OWASP and InfosecGirls shares her thoughts on cloud security. Discover some myth-busting truths about security and the cloud and how to avoid some common perceptions around cloud security. Listen up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>27 Influential Penetration Testers’ around the world</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/influentialpentester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/influentialpentester/</guid>
      <description>Reference</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defcon - AppSec Village 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/appsecvillage_2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/appsecvillage_2020/</guid>
      <description>Title: Running an appsec program with open source projects
We are all heading towards the modernization of applications. However, we still see the companies being impacted with the most common website vulnerabilities like SQL Injection, Sensitive data exposure, security misconfiguration, etc. OWASP has many projects which can be tied seamlessly into the application development pipeline structure. However, firstly we don’t know if the projects exist, second, if we know about the projects, we do not know the exact working of the projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defcon - Red Team Village 2020: Zero Trust</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/redteamvillage_2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/redteamvillage_2020/</guid>
      <description>Title: Zero Trust - A Vision for Securing Cloud and Redefining Security
Reference:- https://redteamvillage.io/day0.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat USA 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/blackhatusa2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/blackhatusa2020/</guid>
      <description>Reference Link: Black Hat USA
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Dark Reading</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/darkreading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/darkreading/</guid>
      <description>Developing Community for Woman Infosec Pros in India
Reference - Dark Reading
https://www.darkreading.com/theedge/developing-community-for-woman-infosec-pros-in-india/b/d-id/1338555</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passionate guide for the web application security journey</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/synopsis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/synopsis/</guid>
      <description>How to get closer to web application security
Reference - https://www.synopsys.com/blogs/software-security/vandana-verma-web-application-security/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to run an Appsec program with open source tools (OWASP)</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/hackkp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/hackkp/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Hac&amp;rsquo;KP Webinar Series_ How to run an Appsec program with open source tools (OWASP)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting into Cyber</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/podcasts/gettingintocyber/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/podcasts/gettingintocyber/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be an InfoSec Speaker - Vandana Verma</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/podcasts/maleallies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/podcasts/maleallies/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Applying OWASP Web Security Testing Guide</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/nulldoha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/nulldoha/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with PortSwigger</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/portswigger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/portswigger/</guid>
      <description>Interview on improving diversity and helping to grow the Indian security community
Reference
https://portswigger.net/daily-swig/infosec-pro-vandana-verma-on-improving-diversity-and-helping-to-grow-the-indian-security-community</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust - A vision for Securing Cloud Delivered Business</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/iitk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/iitk/</guid>
      <description>The #Covid19 pandemic has seen a sudden spur in #Cyber Crimes. With the new world order of WFH and remote working has created new exposures of potential #Cyber-attacks.
The panel will discuss how enterprises can use cloud with zero-trust models to achieve utmost security and safeguard their assets, how zero-trust architecture works with mobile apps in cloud environment.
Must attend webinar for #technology enthusiasts, #entrepreneurs, IT professionals, programmers &amp;amp; students (planning to build their career in IT).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Security Myths with Vandana Verma</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/podcasts/cloudsecuritymyths/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/podcasts/cloudsecuritymyths/</guid>
      <description>There are still lots of misconceptions and myths about Cloud Security. In this episode , Vandana Verma Global Board of Directors at OWASP and InfosecGirls shares her thoughts on cloud security. Discover some myth-busting truths about security and the cloud and how to avoid some common perceptions around cloud security. Listen up!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CII Karnataka Cybersecurity Digital Conference 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/ciikarnataka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/ciikarnataka/</guid>
      <description>Panel discussion on Ethics and Privacy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust:Trust no one, Verify everyone</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/zerotrust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/zerotrust/</guid>
      <description>Cloud Migration is the next big thing. Everyone wants to be in the cloud, but what about security and compliance standards? How do organizations manage both safety and security in the “Cloud Era”? Cloud deployments render the concept that everyone inside of a corporate network should be trusted null and void. Essentially, when it comes to the cloud, everyone is a tenant on a big server farm full of tenants. Thus, the only way forward is the Zero-Trust Model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Security Summit</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/opensummit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/opensummit/</guid>
      <description>Title : Applying OWASP Web Security Testing Guide by Vandana Verma - 12 Jun
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Zero Trust in an organisation to be uncertainty Ready</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/womentech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/womentech/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Implementing Zero Trust in an organisation to be uncertainty Ready&amp;rdquo;
 Reference:-
https://www.womentech.net/en-in/speaker/Vandana/Verma</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Women Tech Network Global Conference: Implementing Zero Trust in an organisation to be uncertainty Ready </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/womentechnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/womentechnet/</guid>
      <description>Session: Implementing Zero Trust in an organisation to be uncertainty Ready
The Current unprecedented situation has changed the IT World forever, no matter what the outcome is, the conceptual changes in the working styles of people are here to stay. The world will never get back to the plane jane everything works only on this building for most of the work environment.
Currently most of the firms have scrambled to enable the workforce to work from home with a certain level of security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vuneraility Assessment for Enterprises</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/cybershikhsa_dsci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/cybershikhsa_dsci/</guid>
      <description>Vuneraility Assessment for Enterprises
Glad to share the #Highlights of Data Security Council of India. DSCI_Connect #CyberShikshaa Virtual Session for Women Students.
The virtual session was extensively attended by over 50 Cyber Shikshaa women students from over 15+ cities #CyberSecurity #Security #Women</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberDay4Girls 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/cyberday_canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/cyberday_canada/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Featured in TimesofIndia</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/timesofindia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/timesofindia/</guid>
      <description>Bug report: The female hackers keeping your work from home systems safe
Reference
https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/city/bengaluru/bug-report-the-female-hackers-keeping-your-work-from-home-systems-safe/articleshow/75968618.cms</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Approaches Post Lockdown</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/securityapproachespostlockdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/securityapproachespostlockdown/</guid>
      <description>It will not be easy to go out even when the lockdown period is over. The way this pandemic is evolving, will take us far away from what we consider normal, and that is for a while. In such a scenario, how shall we be resuming the day to day operations post lockdown? The role of the security team is now more important than ever because of the pandemic and remote work models, the perimeter of the organization has been modified drastically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un-desireable. Un-imaginable. Un-thinkable. We still have the capacity to out beat the threats to your privacy.</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/threatstoprivacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/threatstoprivacy/</guid>
      <description>The time is challenging. No one ever believed that a pandemic would leave us stranded. We will be home for such a long time even though some of us always wanted to work from home but never this way. Most of the organisations are trying to keep the spirits of the employees high and making sure they are safe from the critical situation outside. For many companies especially start ups who didn&amp;rsquo;t have the infrastructure and facilities for the employees and were surviving just on the need base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Suffolk: Living In A World of Zero Trust</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/owaspsufflock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/owaspsufflock/</guid>
      <description>Title: Living In A World of Zero Trust</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarcon 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/sarcon2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/sarcon2020/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to start a Career in AppSec</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/how-to-start-a-career-in-appsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/how-to-start-a-career-in-appsec/</guid>
      <description>Moderator - Niloufer Tamboly,
Panelists
  Mohan Yelnadu
  Katy Anton
  Vandana Verma
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHe CISO IWD 2020 Webinar - Zero trust , why and why not? </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/sheciso/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/sheciso/</guid>
      <description>Webinar:
Zero trust , why and why not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast, Accurate, Agile Security Testing​</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/securitytestinghcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/securitytestinghcl/</guid>
      <description>Fast, Accurate, Agile Security Testing
Moderator: Eitan Worcel
Panelists:
  Vandana Verma Sehgal
  Dragan Pleskonjic
  Laura Guazzelli
  Reference:-
https://www.brighttalk.com/webinar/fast-accurate-agile-security-testing%e2%80%8b-with-appscan-v10/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Manifestation of InfoSec Speaking</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/manifestationofinfosecspeaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/manifestationofinfosecspeaking/</guid>
      <description>Speaking at any Conference is a savoir faire itself. Most often I am asked when and how to start the Infosec speaking journey. My answer to them is fundamental: there is no juncture pre-defined for it. There is no age or qualification criteria to speak at any conference.
I started my journey by speaking at the local meets. Local meets gave me the platform to share my knowledge with a wider audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Exhilarating InfoSec Journey</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/my-exhilarting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/my-exhilarting/</guid>
      <description>Being an information security evangelist, I have been preaching and practicing security for more than a decade. Security is my bread and butter and I love it! I started with consulting roles, where I would use my skills to suggest solutions and improvements. Later, I transitioned to internal security teams which gave me a clear and concise perspective on how organizations manage security risk.
In my opinion, the Information Security Expert can be anyone who has a curiosity towards aspects of technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16 Women Paving the Way in AppSec</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/16womeninappsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/16womeninappsec/</guid>
      <description>Glad to be on the list. Each of the women listed here plays an integral role in the development and progress of application security in their respective organizations. With a wide variety of backgrounds, specialties, and roles, these women are used to pushing boundaries to achieve more.
Check out these 16 inspiring women paving the way in AppSec, and follow them on Twitter to stay on top of their news and events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with CISO MAG</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/cisomag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/cisomag/</guid>
      <description>Closing the Skill Gap With More Women in Cybersecurity
To gain an insight into the lack of women representation, CISO MAG gauged a few women security influencers to understand the cause of this alarming trend. This article is part of a series of interviews from women cybersecurity experts who shed light representation of women in cybersecurity.
Reference https://cisomag.eccouncil.org/closing-the-skill-gap-with-more-women-in-cybersecurity/3/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Seasides 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides/</guid>
      <description>Reference Link: https://2019.owaspseasides.com/events/penetration-testing-workshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A colloquy with Vandana Verma by Sr.Reflectionist Bishakha Jain</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/scit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/scit/</guid>
      <description>https://reflections.scit.edu/?p=4852</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec California 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali/</guid>
      <description>Reference Link: Appsec Cali</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appsec California 2020: Diversity by Design</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/appseccali/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/appseccali/</guid>
      <description>Diversity by Design: Securing the Cyber Workforce Development Lifecycle - Panel
(https://appseccalifornia2020.sched.com/event/XLtw/diversity-by-design-securing-the-cyber-workforce-development-lifecycle)
Panel discussion on the importance of diversity and inclusion in information security, as well as shared experiences and best practices around building diversity and inclusion into the constantly evolving cybersecurity ecosystem.
Topics covered will include the following:
  Professional learning (from both the educator and learning perspectives)
  The importance of diversity on an AppSec team or organization</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps - Virtually Testing </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/devsecops_virtuallytesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/devsecops_virtuallytesting/</guid>
      <description>Why do we need Sec in DevOps? Learn more about it in this video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SACON 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/sacon2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/sacon2020/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Mentoring Monday </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/cybersecuritymentoringmonday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/cybersecuritymentoringmonday/</guid>
      <description>As Chapter Leader at OWASP Bangalore and Asia Lead and Secretary OWASP Women in AppSec(WiA) Vandana kicked off our Appsec themed spell by discussing just how important Appsec is in the modern world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Women in Cybersecurity in India – Instasafe</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/topwomeninindia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/topwomeninindia/</guid>
      <description>On this very note, InstaSafe, this new year brings forth a list of women leaders in this field of technology and cybersecurity as a whole across various sectors based out of India:
Reference:- https://instasafe.com/top-women-in-cybersecurity-in-india/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>52 Influential Cyber Security Bloggers and Speakers by Peerlyst</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/influentialspeaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/influentialspeaker/</guid>
      <description>Glad to be on the list.
Reference - https://www.peerlyst.com/posts/peerlyst-community-ebook-52-influential-cyber-security-bloggers-and-speakers-peerlyst</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop on Web Application Security at c0c0n 2019 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/cocon2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/cocon2019/</guid>
      <description>On 26th September, 2019 infosecgirls organised a one day cyber security conference in collaboration with c0c0n12 hosted by Kerala Police and ISRA on 26th September. The conference was taken place at St. Teresa’s College with 200 Registered participants. The purpose of the conference was to create awareness about cyber security issues in young women population.
Welcome note was given by Ms. Dhanya , HOD IT, St.theresas College which was followed by Presidential Address by Sr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote: Diversity And Inclusion - Not Just A Gender Gap - Vandana Verma</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/addo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/addo/</guid>
      <description>There has been a lot of conversations around diversity and inclusion in the recent past. This is a step in a positive direction. The benefits of diversity in cybersecurity are clear. As an industry, we can do better, we need to do better. We need not only to keep the conversation going but to really place some action behind it. While homogenous teams feel easier to operate in, it can lead to stagnation, or specialisations in some aspects at the expense of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote: Diversity And Inclusion - Not Just A Gender Gap - Vandana Verma </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/appsecdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/appsecdc/</guid>
      <description>There has been a lot of conversations around diversity and inclusion in the recent past. This is a step in a positive direction. The benefits of diversity in cybersecurity are clear. As an industry, we can do better, we need to do better. We need not only to keep the conversation going but to really place some action behind it. While homogenous teams feel easier to operate in, it can lead to stagnation, or specialisations in some aspects at the expense of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global AppSec DC 2019 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsecdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsecdc/</guid>
      <description>Workshop details :
This was a 1-day training course. The Application Security Training is intended for students/professionals interested in making a career in the Information Security domain. This training involved real-world scenarios that every Security Professional must be well versed with. It involved decompiling, real-time analyzing and testing of the applications from a security standpoint.
The training covered understanding the internals of web and mobile applications, Real-time testing of web applications and android applications and a strategic approach to analyze applications for OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities (Web) security issues such as Injections, Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), CSRF Attacks, Insecure API’s, Insecure logging, Insecure communication, Insufficient cryptography, Insecure authentication and Poor code quality and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with ITSP Magazine</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/itsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/itsp/</guid>
      <description>An InfoSec Life | A Conversation With Vandana Verma By Marco Ciappelli
Reference
https://www.itspmagazine.com/itsp-chronicles/an-infosec-life-a-conversation-with-vandana-verma</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winner - Cyber Security Woman Supporter of the Year Award 2019 - Woman CyberJutsu</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/womancyberjutsu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/womancyberjutsu/</guid>
      <description>Cyber Security Woman Supporter of the Year Award 2019 - Woman CyberJutsu, 2019 in &amp;ldquo;Secure Coder&amp;rdquo; Category
Reference
https://womenscyberjutsu.org/page/AWARDWinners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shifting the DevSecOps Culture, Taking away the sugar piece and giving the pile to ants : Defcon - AppSec Village 2019</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/appsecvillage_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/appsecvillage_2019/</guid>
      <description>Title: Shifting the DevSecOps Culture, Taking away the sugar piece and giving the pile to ants
We have been talking about the technical angle of DevSecOps. How do I go about building the DevSecOps culture in the organisation? So far Generally corporates are trying to have all three Plays and teams Dev, Sec and Ops team together. However, the Ideal DevSecOps idea is each individual should know what is happening in the whole process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps and the DevSecOps Survey</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/devopssurvey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/devopssurvey/</guid>
      <description>In this week&amp;rsquo;s DevOps Defined, we talk to Vandana Verma of OWASP Bangalore about a DevSecOps survey she and her team created and why you should take it ASAP to ensure you have a safe secure DevOps environment.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevSecCon: Cloud Security and the Myths Around it</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/devseccon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/devseccon/</guid>
      <description>The talk would be around the general myths we have on Cloud Security and Cloud Computing. Also, we will map the myths with different roles and discuss how to resolve that.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global AppSec Tel Aviv 2019 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/globalappsectelaviv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/globalappsectelaviv/</guid>
      <description>Workshop details :
This was a 1-day training course. The Application Security Training is intended for students/professionals interested in making a career in the Information Security domain. This training involved real-world scenarios that every Security Professional must be well versed with. It involved decompiling, real-time analyzing and testing of the applications from a security standpoint.
The training covered understanding the internals of web and mobile applications, Real-time testing of web applications and android applications and a strategic approach to analyze applications for OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities (Web) security issues such as Injections, Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), CSRF Attacks, Insecure API’s, Insecure logging, Insecure communication, Insufficient cryptography, Insecure authentication and Poor code quality and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Village at c0c0n_2017 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/kidsglove/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/kidsglove/</guid>
      <description>Workshop details :
OWASP Kids village is an Open space exclusively for Kids where there is so much playing around and exploring the insights of Digital World.
Reference: http://is-ra.org/c0c0n/2017/kids_village
Highlights
 OWASP Dissector  Dissector is an event where the kids will be given a platform to knowthe gadgets in a more technical way. They will be assigned a mentor who will completely open up the deviceand make them familiar with thecomponents and their every aspect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bug Bounty World Interviews Vandana Verma</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/bugbountyworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/bugbountyworld/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HackInterview with Vandana</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/hackinterview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/featured/hackinterview/</guid>
      <description>HackInterview with Vandana — document your learning in the form of blogs
Reference
https://medium.com/bugbountywriteup/hackinterview-with-vandana-document-your-learning-in-the-form-of-blogs-3b265ec03be1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Seasides 2019</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides2019/</guid>
      <description>About the Training
In this completely hands-on workshop, you would get to understand the techniques and methodologies that could be applied when performing a web application penetration testing. Throughout this workshop, you would be using Burp Suite tool + OWASP ZAP, which is a conglomerate of distinct tools with powerful features. Apart from gaining familiarity with the tools and the techniques involved in application security testing, you would also get an opportunity to understand some of the common vulnerabilities from the OWASP Top 10 – 2017 list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec California 2019</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali2019/</guid>
      <description>Web Application Penetration Testing: An Introductory Workshop For Developers and Security Professionals At All Levels
In this completely hands-on workshop, you will get to understand the techniques and methodologies that could be applied when performing a web application penetration testing. Throughout this workshop, you will use the Burp Suite tool, which is a conglomerate of distinct tools with powerful features. Apart from gaining familiarity with the tools and the techniques involved in application security testing, you will also get an opportunity to understand some of the common vulnerabilities from the OWASP Top 10 list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec USA 2018 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsecusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsecusa/</guid>
      <description>Why a free workshop? The OWASP volunteer community and our Women in AppSec Committee (WIA) Committee commit to training the leaders behind securing the World Wide Web… That’s YOU! Your learning path starts (or continues) here. We’re excited to form mentorships at this year’s AppSec USA conference.
Breakdown of Topics:
*Interactive one day workshop on how to test applications for security issues. Participants of this course will learn how to do the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Dependency Check</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/owaspottawa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/owaspottawa/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to the Project.To understand what is. Dependency Checker by Supported Languages/tech. Relation to OWASP top 10. Reviewing How it works. Vulnerability Data Source and Evidence based identification, issues and Remediation. How to use Dependency Check Components of Dependency Check. Use Cases of Dependency Check. Enterprise Deployments. How to read the reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHeSecures: Managing Security Operations in Cloud </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/shesecures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/shesecures/</guid>
      <description>Webinar:
Referencd: https://shesecures.org/shesecures-women-in-cybersecurity-webinar/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP AppSec Europe 2018</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/appseceurope2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/talks/appseceurope2018/</guid>
      <description>Thursday, July 5 • 12:30pm - 1:30pm
OWASPWIA (Women In AppSec) hosted a talk and luncheon for all the Ladies
Venue:
Byron- 4th Floor QEII Centre Broad Sanctuary, Westminster, London. SW1P 3EE
Reference:- https://2018.appsec.eu/about/women-in-appsec</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manager Choice Award - IBM</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/managerchoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/awards/managerchoice/</guid>
      <description>Manager&amp;rsquo;s Choice Award for demonstrating the Unite to get it done now
Reference
https://leadmind.inteligenca.com/cswy2020/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nullcon 2018</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/nullcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/nullcon/</guid>
      <description>This Training is intended for Women Infosec professionals interested in making a career in the Information Security domain. This training involves real world scenarios that every Security Professional must be well versed with. It involves decompiling, real-time analyzing and testing of the applications from security standpoint.
Workshop by OWASP (Limited Seats).
Reference https://nullcon.net/website/goa-2018/schedule.php#conferenceDay1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Security Operations in the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/brightalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/webinars/brightalk/</guid>
      <description>The moment an organization starts making a move to Cloud, the way they look at their security changes as well. A traditional security operation is more focused towards a bunch of solutions such as Firewalls, IDS/IPS, Anti-Malware, etc. Security Operations in the cloud is more about following the pragmatic approach. It is about using effectively the huge set of already available resources in the cloud to effectively harden, monitor and defend cloud infrastructures and applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women Roundtable hosted by Target</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/swati/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/paneldiscussion/swati/</guid>
      <description>Topic: ‘The Emerging trends in cyber security’.
Panelists
Vandana Verma, Manager Information Security
Priya Murthi, Project Manager, Shell
Minatee Mishra, Lead Engineer, Philips
Nidhi Agarwal, Lead Technical Architect, Target
Venue: Target Corporation India, Manyata Tech Park, Bangalore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/owaspspotlightseries/spotlight20/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
