<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BLOG POSTS on Vandana Verma</title>
    <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BLOG POSTS on Vandana Verma</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Vandana Verma</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Consumer identities in Modern Digital World (CIAM)</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/ciam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/ciam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Digitization is the way to go However, while the consumers are increasing, we still follow the primitive approach and have always been taking too much information from the users like Email Address, Username, Address, Password and much more during the first interaction itself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, security is becoming equally big concern for the organizations and users. Usability is severely impacted with applying the highest level of security on every user interaction which results in a poor user experience. So, balancing both becomes the priority for any organization to keep the user base intact.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrate ‘You’ - Be relentless, fearless, voice out!</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/relentlessyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/relentlessyou/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let’s start with a beautiful quote by Ruth Bader Ginsburg -“Women will have achieved true equality when men share with them the responsibility of bringing up the next generation”. 2020 has taught that a family can have 2 heroes in the same home and share responsibilities while meting differences. Supporting and uplifting each other, leads to co-growth which can be a strong influence personally and the backbone for a positive career path.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2021 LENS INTO CYBERSECURITY TRENDS</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/2021lens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/2021lens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2020 was a year like never before. We all witnessed the twists and turns in our lives. It did have a torrential impact on the cyber security ecosystem too. Although everyone quickly adapted to the new world and embraced the use of technology to work from home, but deep down it meant there was a whole new attack to be guarded against- inadequate preparedness. This led to the paradigm shift from the highly forecasted AI and ML taking precedence whereas it was cloud migration or computing taking the top priority.With such a shift, 2021 brings hopes and new beginnings to organisations looking to re-model to the new way of working and adapting to the current solutions. Listed here are few technological aspects which will take primacy over the workforce ecosystems: -&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integration Reciepe : IBM IGI with IBM Security Verify </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/recipe_igiverify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/recipe_igiverify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently I have been experimenting with various IBM product integrations and I posted a reciepe in IBM Community portal for integration of IBM IGI with IBM Security Verify.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This recipe talks about the ideal set of steps that someone has to take to connect the two applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is a direct link to the article.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://community.ibm.com/community/user/security/communities/community-home/digestviewer/viewthread?MessageKey=753ba57a-d19c-4959-9c26-213ac8c24d40&amp;amp;CommunityKey=e7c36119-46d7-42f2-97a9-b44f0cc89c6d&amp;amp;tab=digestviewer#bm753ba57a-d19c-4959-9c26-213ac8c24d40&#34;&gt;Recipe for IBM Security Verify Governance (IGI) and IBM Security Verify for Workforce IAM Integration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running an AppSec Program with Open Source (OWASP) Projects</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/runningappsecprogram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/runningappsecprogram/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are all heading towards modernisation of applications. However, we still see the vulnerabilities like SQL Injection, Sensitive data exposure, and security misconfiguration etc. When the loopholes  in applications (such as legacy, desktop, web, mobile, micro services) are exploited, it can give malicious actors access to the organisation&amp;rsquo;s data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a fact that Breaches will happen and security flaws will exist, however what we can do is minimise the chances. This is when the AppSec program comes into picture.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust:Trust no one, Verify everyone</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/zerotrust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/zerotrust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cloud Migration is the next big thing. Everyone wants to be in the cloud, but what about security and compliance standards? How do organizations manage both safety and security in the “Cloud Era”? Cloud deployments render the concept that everyone inside of a corporate network should be trusted null and void. Essentially, when it comes to the cloud, everyone is a tenant on a big server farm full of tenants. Thus, the only way forward is the Zero-Trust Model.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Approaches Post Lockdown</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/securityapproachespostlockdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/securityapproachespostlockdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It will not be easy to go out even when the lockdown period is over. The way this pandemic is evolving, will take us far away from what we consider normal, and that is for a while. In such a scenario, how shall we be resuming the day to day operations post lockdown? The role of the security team is now more important than ever because of the pandemic and remote work models, the perimeter of the organization has been modified drastically. Cyber attacks are on the rise, the need to manage many more devices, applications, etc. InfoSec is more important than ever. Most of the companies were able to pull off the remote working with all the struggle with technologies involved. In such a case what a CISO can do by keeping in mind how strategically breaking down the whole organisation infrastructure to cater to remote working conditions, categorizing and prioritizing things. Also looking at where the attacks could come from (having a clear threat model) and measure everything&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Un-desireable. Un-imaginable. Un-thinkable. We still have the capacity to out beat the threats to your privacy.</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/threatstoprivacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/threatstoprivacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The time is challenging. No one ever believed that a pandemic would leave us stranded. We will be home for such a long time even though some of us always wanted to work from home but never this way. Most of the organisations are trying to keep the spirits of the employees high and making sure they are safe from the critical situation outside. For many companies especially start ups who didn&amp;rsquo;t have the infrastructure and facilities for the employees and were surviving just on the need base.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Manifestation of InfoSec Speaking</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/manifestationofinfosecspeaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/manifestationofinfosecspeaking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Speaking at any Conference is a savoir faire itself. Most often I am asked when and how to start the Infosec speaking journey. My answer to them is fundamental: there is no juncture pre-defined for it. There is no age or qualification criteria to speak at any conference.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I started my journey by speaking at the local meets. Local meets gave me the platform to share my knowledge with a wider audience. It’s one of the best places to start and connect with the crowd as well as address the questions coming thereafter. I was absolutely nervous delivering my first talk at a meetup. Although I had delivered multiple sessions within my organisation,I still hesitated from making eye contact with the audience.  My first session was on information security news bytes, the topic was very simple as I just had to look up the latest infosec news from the various news sources, however it was not so easy for me to speak with a loose assemblage of diverse groups of people. The only thing that bothered me constantly was what if I said something wrong. Eventually, I kept on giving talks on various topics, and everytime I spoke at a meet or a conference, it made me more confident.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Exhilarating InfoSec Journey</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/my-exhilarting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/blogs/my-exhilarting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Being an information security evangelist, I have been preaching and practicing security for more than a decade. Security is my bread and butter and I love it! I started with consulting roles, where I would use my skills to suggest solutions and improvements. Later, I transitioned to internal security teams which gave me a clear and concise perspective on how organizations manage security risk.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, the Information Security Expert can be anyone who has a curiosity towards aspects of technology. You need to build on that curiosity and spend a lot of time understanding the inner working of these technologies. Information security is a multi-speciality domain and hence specialists are very common. You can be an expert in a specific area of Information Security, for instance a Malware Analyst (an expert in areas such as Dissecting Malicious software and Reverse engineering) or an Application Security person (an expert in application security, code review, or DevSecOps processes).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
