<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trainings on Vandana Verma</title>
    <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trainings on Vandana Verma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Vandana Verma</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Security Testing Workshop 2021 for CSQA</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/securitytestingqa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/securitytestingqa/</guid>
      <description>About the Workshop
Showcasing Security Testing essentials, OWASP Project, different tools and approaches for Security Testing.
Attendees will learn:
 What is Application security Testing and its importance OWASP Security Testing Projects, tools and approaches How to start with Security Testing  Reference Link: https://www.townscript.com/e/csqa-security-test-workshop
Video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global AppSec 2020 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/globalappsecsf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/globalappsecsf/</guid>
      <description>About the Training
This Training is intended for students/professionals interested in making a career in the Information Security domain. This training involves real world scenarios that every Security Professional must be well versed with. It involves decompiling, real-time analyzing and testing of the applications from security standpoint.
Reference https://events.bizzabo.com/OWASPGlobalAppSec/agenda/session/325430</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Seasides 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides/</guid>
      <description>Reference Link: https://2019.owaspseasides.com/events/penetration-testing-workshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec California 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali/</guid>
      <description>Reference Link: Appsec Cali</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop on Web Application Security at c0c0n 2019 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/cocon2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/cocon2019/</guid>
      <description>On 26th September, 2019 infosecgirls organised a one day cyber security conference in collaboration with c0c0n12 hosted by Kerala Police and ISRA on 26th September. The conference was taken place at St. Teresa’s College with 200 Registered participants. The purpose of the conference was to create awareness about cyber security issues in young women population.
Welcome note was given by Ms. Dhanya , HOD IT, St.theresas College which was followed by Presidential Address by Sr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global AppSec DC 2019 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsecdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsecdc/</guid>
      <description>Workshop details :
This was a 1-day training course. The Application Security Training is intended for students/professionals interested in making a career in the Information Security domain. This training involved real-world scenarios that every Security Professional must be well versed with. It involved decompiling, real-time analyzing and testing of the applications from a security standpoint.
The training covered understanding the internals of web and mobile applications, Real-time testing of web applications and android applications and a strategic approach to analyze applications for OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities (Web) security issues such as Injections, Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), CSRF Attacks, Insecure API’s, Insecure logging, Insecure communication, Insufficient cryptography, Insecure authentication and Poor code quality and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global AppSec Tel Aviv 2019 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/globalappsectelaviv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/globalappsectelaviv/</guid>
      <description>Workshop details :
This was a 1-day training course. The Application Security Training is intended for students/professionals interested in making a career in the Information Security domain. This training involved real-world scenarios that every Security Professional must be well versed with. It involved decompiling, real-time analyzing and testing of the applications from a security standpoint.
The training covered understanding the internals of web and mobile applications, Real-time testing of web applications and android applications and a strategic approach to analyze applications for OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities (Web) security issues such as Injections, Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), CSRF Attacks, Insecure API’s, Insecure logging, Insecure communication, Insufficient cryptography, Insecure authentication and Poor code quality and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Village at c0c0n_2017 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/kidsglove/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/kidsglove/</guid>
      <description>Workshop details :
OWASP Kids village is an Open space exclusively for Kids where there is so much playing around and exploring the insights of Digital World.
Reference: http://is-ra.org/c0c0n/2017/kids_village</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Seasides 2019</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides2019/</guid>
      <description>About the Training
In this completely hands-on workshop, you would get to understand the techniques and methodologies that could be applied when performing a web application penetration testing. Throughout this workshop, you would be using Burp Suite tool + OWASP ZAP, which is a conglomerate of distinct tools with powerful features. Apart from gaining familiarity with the tools and the techniques involved in application security testing, you would also get an opportunity to understand some of the common vulnerabilities from the OWASP Top 10 – 2017 list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec California 2019</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali2019/</guid>
      <description>Web Application Penetration Testing: An Introductory Workshop For Developers and Security Professionals At All Levels
In this completely hands-on workshop, you will get to understand the techniques and methodologies that could be applied when performing a web application penetration testing. Throughout this workshop, you will use the Burp Suite tool, which is a conglomerate of distinct tools with powerful features. Apart from gaining familiarity with the tools and the techniques involved in application security testing, you will also get an opportunity to understand some of the common vulnerabilities from the OWASP Top 10 list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec USA 2018 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsecusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsecusa/</guid>
      <description>Why a free workshop? The OWASP volunteer community and our Women in AppSec Committee (WIA) Committee commit to training the leaders behind securing the World Wide Web… That’s YOU! Your learning path starts (or continues) here. We’re excited to form mentorships at this year’s AppSec USA conference.
Breakdown of Topics:
*Interactive one day workshop on how to test applications for security issues. Participants of this course will learn how to do the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nullcon 2018</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/nullcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/nullcon/</guid>
      <description>This Training is intended for Women Infosec professionals interested in making a career in the Information Security domain. This training involves real world scenarios that every Security Professional must be well versed with. It involves decompiling, real-time analyzing and testing of the applications from security standpoint.
Workshop by OWASP (Limited Seats).
Reference https://nullcon.net/website/goa-2018/schedule.php#conferenceDay1</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
