<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trainings on Vandana Verma</title>
    <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trainings on Vandana Verma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Vandana Verma</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Global AppSec 2020 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/globalappsecsf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/globalappsecsf/</guid>
      <description>This Training is intended for students/professionals interested in making a career in the Information Security domain. This training involves real world scenarios that every Security Professional must be well versed with. It involves decompiling, real-time analyzing and testing of the applications from security standpoint.
Reference https://events.bizzabo.com/OWASPGlobalAppSec/agenda/session/325430</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Seasides 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides/</guid>
      <description>Reference Link: https://2019.owaspseasides.com/events/penetration-testing-workshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec California 2020</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali/</guid>
      <description>Reference Link: Appsec Cali</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Seasides 2019</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/owaspseasides2019/</guid>
      <description>About the Training
In this completely hands-on workshop, you would get to understand the techniques and methodologies that could be applied when performing a web application penetration testing. Throughout this workshop, you would be using Burp Suite tool + OWASP ZAP, which is a conglomerate of distinct tools with powerful features. Apart from gaining familiarity with the tools and the techniques involved in application security testing, you would also get an opportunity to understand some of the common vulnerabilities from the OWASP Top 10 – 2017 list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec California 2019</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsec_cali2019/</guid>
      <description>Web Application Penetration Testing: An Introductory Workshop For Developers and Security Professionals At All Levels
In this completely hands-on workshop, you will get to understand the techniques and methodologies that could be applied when performing a web application penetration testing. Throughout this workshop, you will use the Burp Suite tool, which is a conglomerate of distinct tools with powerful features. Apart from gaining familiarity with the tools and the techniques involved in application security testing, you will also get an opportunity to understand some of the common vulnerabilities from the OWASP Top 10 list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec USA 2018 </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsecusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/appsecusa/</guid>
      <description>Why a free workshop? The OWASP volunteer community and our Women in AppSec Committee (WIA) Committee commit to training the leaders behind securing the World Wide Web… That’s YOU! Your learning path starts (or continues) here. We’re excited to form mentorships at this year’s AppSec USA conference.
Breakdown of Topics:
*Interactive one day workshop on how to test applications for security issues. Participants of this course will learn how to do the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nullcon 2018</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/nullcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/trainings/nullcon/</guid>
      <description>This Training is intended for Women Infosec professionals interested in making a career in the Information Security domain. This training involves real world scenarios that every Security Professional must be well versed with. It involves decompiling, real-time analyzing and testing of the applications from security standpoint.
Workshop by OWASP (Limited Seats).
Reference https://nullcon.net/website/goa-2018/schedule.php#conferenceDay1</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
