<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A day in the life of an Entrepreneur on Vandana Verma</title>
    <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/</link>
    <description>Recent content in A day in the life of an Entrepreneur on Vandana Verma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Vandana Verma</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 12 - Pawan Desai</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/pawandesai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/pawandesai/</guid>
      <description>Pawan Desai
https://www.linkedin.com/in/pawan-desai-5455562/
https://twitter.com/pawandesai
Bio:-
Co-founder &amp;amp; CEO - MitKat Advisory Services, Cyber Security, IVLP fellow, Submariner, Advisor AllMiles, Visiting faculty at NMIMS MitKat Risk Intelligence and Monitoring Engine, Certified Corporate Director
Learning for Mentees:
  Do what you love
  Mediocrity will kill the culture, Don&amp;rsquo;t accept Mediocrity, Work with people who want to work for a cause
  Your work doesn&amp;rsquo;t define you. To be known for is who and what you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 11 - Aseem Jakhar</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/aseem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/aseem/</guid>
      <description>Aseem Jakhar
https://www.linkedin.com/in/aseemjakhar/
https://twitter.com/aseemjakhar
Bio:-
Entrepreneur | IoT security | Co-Founder - Payatu, hardwear.io, nullcon.net, null.co.in | Author - EXPLIoT framework
Learning for Mentees:
Try, Fail, Try Again - You will win</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 10 - Shubham Mittal </title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shubham/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shubham/</guid>
      <description>Shubham Mittal
https://www.linkedin.com/in/upgoingstar/ https://twitter.com/upgoingstar
Bio:-
Co-Founder at RedHunt Labs | BlackHat Asia Review Board Member
Learning for Mentees:-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 9 - Aaron Rinehart</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/aaronrinehart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/aaronrinehart/</guid>
      <description>Aaron Rinehart
https://twitter.com/aaronrinehart
https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaronsrinehart/
Bio:-
Aaron has been expanding the possibilities of Chaos Engineering in its application to other safety- critical portions of the IT domain notably cybersecurity. He began pioneering the application of Security in Chaos Engineering during his tenure as the Chief Security Architect at the largest private healthcare company in the world, UnitedHealth Group (UHG). While at UHG Aaron released ChaoSlingr, one of the first open source software releases focused on using Chaos Engineering in cybersecurity to build more resilient systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 7 - Dhillon Kannabhiran</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/dhillon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/dhillon/</guid>
      <description>Dhillon Kannabhiran
https://www.linkedin.com/in/l33tdawg/
Bio:-
Dhillon Andrew Kannabhiran (@l33tdawg on Twitter) is the Founder and Chief Executive Officer of Hack in The Box (http://www.hitb.org), organiser of the HITBSecConf series of network security conferences which has been held annually for over a decade in various countries including Malaysia, The Netherlands and the UAE.
Prior to quitting his day job to lead the HITB team on crazy adventures around the world, Dhillon started off at the height of the dotcom craze as a technology journalist with PC World, ZDnet, MIS Asia and CNet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 8 - Amar Singh</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/amarsingh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/amarsingh/</guid>
      <description>Amar Singh
https://www.linkedin.com/in/chiefinfosec/
Bio:-
Amar Singh is a CEO, CISO, Cyber Crisis &amp;amp; Incident Response Practitioner, Speaker &amp;amp; Co-Founder Cyber Management Alliance.
Amar is an industry acknowledged expert and public speaker and is regularly invited to speak and share his insights by some of the largest and most respected organisations in the world including The BBC, The Economist’s Intelligence Unit, The Financial Times, SC Magazine, InfoSec Magazine, Computer Weekly, The Register and the Al-Jazeera English Channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6 - Keenan Skelly</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/keenan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/keenan/</guid>
      <description>Keenan Skelly
https://www.linkedin.com/in/keenan-skelly/
Bio:-
• Co-Founder &amp;amp; CEO - shyftED, Inc.
• President and CEO - Spark Security Solutions, Inc
• Strategic Advisor to CEO - Circadence Corp.
• Director, Board of Directors – Night Lion Security
• Advisor, Women in Cybersecurity Advisory Council – SC Media
• Games Master - Women’s Society of Cyberjutsu
Ms. Skelly has twenty years’ experience in providing security and management solutions across a wide array of platforms to include personnel, physical, and cyber security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 5 - Mari Galloway</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/mari/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/mari/</guid>
      <description>Mari Galloway
https://www.linkedin.com/in/themarigalloway/
https://twitter.com/marigalloway
Bio:-
Mari is the CEO and a founding board member for the Women&amp;rsquo;s Society of Cyberjutsu (WSC), one of the fastest growing 501c3 non-profit cybersecurity communities dedicated to bringing more women and girls to cyber. WSC provides its members with the resources and support required to enter and advance as a cybersecurity professional. Mari began her cyber career with Accenture where she excelled as a Network Engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 4 - Takaharu Ogasa</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/takaharu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/takaharu/</guid>
      <description>Takaharu Ogasa https://twitter.com/TakaharuOgasa https://www.linkedin.com/in/takaharu-ogasa-a245b7b5/
Bio: Takaharu is the Founder of Security Initiative, a start-up and a Cyber Security consultancy. He is also the chapter leader for OWASP Sandai Chapter.
Learning for the Mentees:-
Link to the Previous Episodes: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R75Oye_LIaI&amp;amp;list=PLUKo5k_oSrfMzA0_VbOJjKh1AViSYcNrr</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3 - Bryson Bort</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/bryson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/bryson/</guid>
      <description>Bio:
Bryson is the Founder of SCYTHE, a start-up building a next generation attack emulation platform, and GRIMM, a cybersecurity consultancy, and Co-Founder of the ICS Village, a non-profit advancing awareness of industrial control system security. He is a Senior Fellow for Cybersecurity and National Security at R Street and the National Security Institute and an Advisor to the Army Cyber Institute. As a U.S. Army Officer, he served as a Battle Captain and Brigade Engineering Officer in support of Operation Iraqi Freedom before leaving the Army as a Captain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2 - Shira Shamban</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shira/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shira/</guid>
      <description>Shira Shamban
https://twitter.com/ShambanIT​
Bio:
Shira Shamban is a security researcher and technical expert with a focus on cloud security. Currently, she is the co-founder and CEO of Solvo. Shira started her professional career in #cybersecurity​ as a military officer in the elite intelligence unit 8200 of the Israel Defense Force. During her 13-year service in the unit, Shira acquired hands-on experience in cybersecurity and intelligence operations while earning an engineering degree from Tel-Aviv University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1 - Shivangi Nadkarni</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shivangi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shivangi/</guid>
      <description>Shivani Nadkarni (Co-founder &amp;amp; CEO - Arrka)
https://twitter.com/shivanginadkarn​
Bio: Shivangi has over 24 years of experience in the domains of Information Security &amp;amp; Risk Management, E-Commerce &amp;amp; Networking across multiple geographies. She has earlier worked with organizations like Wipro &amp;amp; Sify handling a variety of roles and heading different Lines of Business. She was instrumental in setting up the first licensed Certifying Authority in India – in association with VeriSign. She has authored the Privacy Book of Knowledge (PBoK) for DSCI for their DCPP certification program.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
