<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leader Speak on Vandana Verma</title>
    <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Leader Speak on Vandana Verma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Vandana Verma</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3: A day in the life of an Entrepreneur - Bryson Bort</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/bryson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/bryson/</guid>
      <description>Bryson Bort https://www.linkedin.com/in/brysonbort/​ https://twitter.com/brysonbort​
Bio: Bryson is the Founder of SCYTHE, a start-up building a next generation attack emulation platform, and GRIMM, a cybersecurity consultancy, and Co-Founder of the ICS Village, a non-profit advancing awareness of industrial control system security. He is a Senior Fellow for Cybersecurity and National Security at R Street and the National Security Institute and an Advisor to the Army Cyber Institute. As a U.S. Army Officer, he served as a Battle Captain and Brigade Engineering Officer in support of Operation Iraqi Freedom before leaving the Army as a Captain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2: A day in the life of an Entrepreneur - Shira Shamban</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shira/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shira/</guid>
      <description>Shira Shamban https://twitter.com/ShambanIT​ https://www.linkedin.com/in/shira-sha...​
Bio: Shira Shamban is a security researcher and technical expert with a focus on cloud security. Currently, she is the co-founder and CEO of Solvo. Shira started her professional career in #cybersecurity​ as a military officer in the elite intelligence unit 8200 of the Israel Defense Force. During her 13-year service in the unit, Shira acquired hands-on experience in cybersecurity and intelligence operations while earning an engineering degree from Tel-Aviv University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1: A day in the life of an Entrepreneur - Shivangi Nadkarni</title>
      <link>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shivangi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infosecvandana.com/leaderspeak/shivangi/</guid>
      <description>Shira Shamban https://twitter.com/ShambanIT​ https://www.linkedin.com/in/shira-sha...​
Bio: Shivani Nadkarni (Co-founder &amp;amp; CEO - Arrka) https://twitter.com/shivanginadkarn​ https://www.linkedin.com/in/shivangin...​
Bio: Shivangi has over 24 years of experience in the domains of Information Security &amp;amp; Risk Management, E-Commerce &amp;amp; Networking across multiple geographies. She has earlier worked with organizations like Wipro &amp;amp; Sify handling a variety of roles and heading different Lines of Business. She was instrumental in setting up the first licensed Certifying Authority in India – in association with VeriSign.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
